<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Sharla Gelfand</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Sharla Gelfand</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright &amp;copy; 2017 - Sharla Gelfand</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Tidying and mapping Toronto open data</title>
      <link>/posts/tidying-toronto-open-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/tidying-toronto-open-data/</guid>
      <description>According to the 2017 Open Cities Index Results, the city of Toronto ranks second in Canada in terms of open data maturity. With 250+ data sets, this initiative makes it easy to access information on business, culture, environment, finance, health, parks + rec, public safety, transportation, and more.
I was curious to poke around open data and learn something new along the way, both in terms of Toronto and the R ecosystem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are people obsessed with Virgos?</title>
      <link>/posts/virgos/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/virgos/</guid>
      <description>As you may know, I like astrology. Astro Poets is a great twitter account run by two poets who post painfully accurate descriptions and commentary on the twelve zodiac signs.
Today they tweeted that a Viirgo wrote in asking if people like tweets about Virgos more.
Now, I’m not a Virgo, and they definitely made fun of the person for asking – but now I gotta know.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tidy Text Mining with Horoscopes</title>
      <link>/posts/horoscopes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/horoscopes/</guid>
      <description>If you’ve ever talked to me for ~10 seconds, chances are I’m wondering what your zodiac sign is – any longer than that, I’ve probably asked you.
Astrology is not for everyone, but it’s definitely for me! YMMV on different sites, and horoscope quality definitely varies, but I’ve found an astrologer that I’m a pretty big fan of – Chani Nicholas!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peppermint</title>
      <link>/posts/peppermint/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/peppermint/</guid>
      <description>👋
A few weeks ago I went to rstudio::conf() and came home sans wallet, sans keys, but plus a lot of inspiration to actually work on personal projects and try out some of the new (and not-so-new!) things that RStudio has to offer. I’d touched Shiny a few times but honestly maybe hadn’t used RMarkdown since the Sweave days.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>